KIMBERLY PRICE

(623) 455-0966 ♦ kiprc@aol.com

EXECUTIVE ASSISTANT

Executive Assistant with 10 years of experience providing administrative coordinating and executive support to Development and Acquisition Executives, Partners, Vice Presidents and Community Development/Planning, Zoning, Building Safety and Commercial Leasing Divisions. Extensive experience with public policy and regulations, project coordinating, organizing, planning, implementing, and reviewing various demographic reports, re-development, site development and building development narratives, submittals and design packages, and purchase agreements ranging in complexity. Major talents in complex calendar management, communication coordination, paper and electronic document organization and filing, travel arrangements, report generation and any and all office administrative tasks. Outstanding organizational, implementation and planning skills. Detail-driven and analytically oriented with a proven ability to multitask in fast-paced, deadline driven environments.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

WORD EXCEL POWERPOINT OUTLOOK | ELECTRONIC FILING AND CATEGORIZING | EXPENSE CERTIFICATION REPORT ANALYSIS | BUDGET PREPARATION | MEETING NOTATION | EVENT AND TRAVEL COORDINATION

EXPERIENCE

RED Development, Phoenix AZ Leasing Administrator

January 2011 – December 2012

- Provide Executive support and coordination to the Leasing Partner, Managing Vice President of Leasing,
 Managing Vice President of Asset Management, Vice President of Leasing, Vice President of Marketing and Communications.
- Extensive and complicated calendar management and coordination involving national meetings, various players and multifaceted materials accumulation and organization.
- Assist in the planning, coordinating and securing of RED Development's yearly attendance of the International Council of Shopping Centers venue in Las Vegas, New York and Chicago involving large shipments of materials, securing several travel arrangements, preparing for hundreds of meetings, coordinating catering detail and manage booth assembly and partition congregation areas.
- Responsible for running multifarious, confidential financial reports to distribute within the company and outside investment, brokerage, and financial institutions in several different states.
- Research for and build complex binders of information containing leasing projections, re-development reports, marketing materials, traffic analysis, site plans, demographics and budget projections for use by senior executives, investors, agents and departments, companywide covering 12 states and 42 properties.
- Program administrator for the Clarita/Nielsen demographic and economic reporting downloads for document assembly, production and distribution.
- Assist the Marketing Department in identifying property related strengths, weaknesses, opportunities and threats covering 42 properties across 12 states.
- Manage RED's website uploading information consisting of site plans, contacts, news releases and tenant location. In addition, upload marketing information on IPads for leasing associates.
- Manage department expenditures keeping within budgeted parameters and stabilization projections.
- Address partners and senior management in quarterly meetings with leasing projections, site plans and tenant sales reporting.
- Compile complex, detailed package scenarios for use by Asset Management in the projection of stabilizing properties, investment possibilities and loan re-financing.

KIMBERLY PRICE

Administrative Assistant

- Provide administrative support to Senior Executives including Operations Manager, Chief Financial Officer, Construction Manager, and Design Department Manager.
- Managed complex calendars, scheduled meetings and appointments, and planned large complex events involving travel, catering and entertainment.
- Responsible for communication management including addressing the public, answering calls, sending emails, typing letters, handle sensitive legal, confidential HR documents and building PowerPoint presentations for all departments.
- Built complex binders of information containing building code information, construction plans, and fire and building codes for use by Senior Executives and outside government agencies and inspectors.
- Tracked hours of work by the design team using Excel spreadsheets personally built, formulated and maintained.
- Maintained files of construction documents, building plans, fire codes, and compliance certifications.

Town of Buckeye, Buckeye, AZ

November 2005 – January 2010

Permit Technician/Assistant to the Chief Building Official

- Worked Directly with and for the Chief Building Official, Town Council, Town Fire Chief, Fire Marshall, Economic Development and Public Works.
- Processed vertical construction, infrastructure, and right-of-way permits by examining submittal documents including site and building plans, project narratives and project cost certifications.
- Assisted in Designing a One-Stop-Shop for Planning Zoning and Building Safety submittals and plan permitting.
- Assisted with business licensing in the collection of application requirements.
- Contributed narrative details for Economic Development, Planning and Zoning and Building Safety to submit and present to Town Council for approval.
- Committee member for the implementation of procedures for various types of submittals improving the process by significantly diminishing the timeline between submittal and final approvals.
- Constant interaction with citizens, project leads, various engineers, various contractors and all Town officials including Town Council, Town Manager, Town Clerk and Town Engineer.
- Primary lead for all infrastructure and industrial submittals and permits.
- Projected Community Development budgeting needs with Permitting Supervisor, Chief Building Official and Planning and Zoning Director for submittal to the Town Council.
- Main contact for citizens, contractors and developers with disputes, complaints and concerns.
- Advised developers and engineers how to obtain bonds, assured water supply certificates, storm water pollution prevention plans, dust control permits, traffic analysis, soils reports, and environmental assessments.
- Maintained weekly revenue flows in a balance sheet for Finance Department and Town Council.
- Organized and maintained filing system for 18,000+ plan library.

Chicago Title, Phoenix, AZ

March 2005 - August 2005

Development and Housing Representative - Executive Assistant to the Director

- Responsible for communicating all new development and housing projects to the entire company.
- Answered department related calls, managed calendars, development schedules and Department of Real Estate hearings for clients and representatives.
- Scheduled complex meeting involving various people with many different project related agendas.
- Compiled information to produce public reports for public record approved by the Department of Real Estate.
- Assisted clients in city, state and government related submittal processes, certifications achievements and advised proper protocol when addressing the Department of Real Estate.
- Organized meetings for the assurance and communication of time line efficiency, construction schedules, submittal requirements and deadlines and contact distribution.

KIMBERLY PRICE

• Reviewed title report schedules for accuracy against documentation reported.

Montalbano Homes, Scottsdale, AZ

November 2004 – March 2005

Development and Acquisitions Coordinator

- Compiled submittal packages according to City and Town requirements for permitting.
- Recruited, awarded and managed subcontractors, engineers and consultants pertinent to site development activities for residential subdivisions.
- Developed and coordinated subsequent community information needed for the Sales and Marketing department to facilitate the Public Report processes, advertising campaigns and public announcements.
- Updated project records for corporate office use and bank loan terms, conditions, and requirements.
- Communicated with city and county officials to identify standards, regulations, zoning, and information for permitting and site work planning processes.
- Ensured accuracy of agreements; examined terms and conditions and project timelines.
- Ordered updated title reports for surveyors and engineers to complete the process of final plat development.
- Organized and administrated meetings to meet construction schedules and inspection expectations.

Reynen & Bardis Development, Sparks, NV Land Development Coordinator

March 2002 - August 2004

- Provided administrative support to the Land Development Manager and division President.
- Reconciled budgets, monitored change orders, and reviewed invoices.
- Recruited all subcontractors and prepared bid packages.
- Arranged and coordinated preconstruction meetings.
- Studied construction agreements for terms and conditions pertinent to timelines, conflict management, and change order circumstances.
- Followed the as-builts through the municipality for signatures.
- Ordered bonds, certificate of insurance, and researched Certificate of Occupancy information for bond release and reduction.
- Notarized and facilitate the recordation of all plans and documentation pertinent to land acquisitions and development.
- Facilitated weekly meeting with city engineer staff.

EDUCATION

University of Phoenix, Phoenix, AZ

November 2010

Bachelor of Science in Business Management

AFFILIATIONS AND INTERESTS

International Building Code Professional, National Notary Association, Volunteer for Mosaic Foundation, Phoenix Rescue Mission, Hope World Wide, Feed the Hungry and Veterans Administration, Military and Central Intelligence history, running, biking and hiking

COMPUTER PROGRAMS

Microsoft Word, Excel, Outlook, PowerPoint, MRI, Certify, Publisher, Visio, Adobe, iTunes